trefootball.com 2016-11-05

# Tre Football

**Information that we collect**

For each visitor to trefootball.com, our web server collects the following type of information for statistical purposes:

  * The number of users who visit the website
  * The date and time of the visits
  * The pages accessed
  * The user’s top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .uk etc)
  * The previous site visited
  * The type of browser used
  * The user’s operating system (Windows, Mac etc)

This is anonymous statistical data and no attempt will be made to identify users. Data is solely used to evaluate our website and to improve the content we display to you.

In addition to the information that we collect upon your initial access to our site, we may ask you for personal information at other times such as when you enter promotions or contests, when you respond to a survey or when you participate in a blog discussion.

External links 

Some sponsors and advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. trefootball.com does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those sponsors and advertisers or web sites are not covered by this privacy policy.

**Collection of personal information**

When you email us:

  * We will record your email address.
  * We will only use your email address for the purpose for which you provided it.
  * It will not be added to an external mailing list unless requested• We will not use your email address for any other purpose
  * We will not disclose it without your consent.

Other personal information collected by us (for example through the use of an online form) will only:

  * Be collected by lawful and fair means.
  * Be used for a lawful purpose.
  * Be collected with your consent, and.
  * The purpose for collection is clear and explicit.

**How we capture information**

We use technology called cookies when you visit our site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website can transfer to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping. Your cookie may be sent at various times during your visit to our web site and may be updated as you access the many different areas.

Most Internet browsers are pre-set to accept cookies. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can adjust your Internet browser to refuse cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used.

**Use of collected information**

The information we collect (including information contained in your cookie) may be used to provide such capabilities as personalization services, interactive communications, and personalized communication between you and the content you prefer. We may also use the information to estimate the size of our audience and measure certain traffic patterns, to track the progress and number of entries in our promotions and contests, to track visits to and business conducted and to notify our visitors about updates to our web site.

We may occasionally contact you with information regarding special events at trefootball.com. If you ever receive a type of communication that you would not like to receive, you will have the option to unsubscribe from such communication (usually at the bottom of the page)

. **With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?**

trefootball.com does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s).

If we intend to share such information, you will be notified prior to the collection of that information. If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest.

**Security of information**

Information that we capture is passed through a secure server using encryption technology which scrambles the information to ensure it is protected over the internet.

**Terms of use**

As a visitor to this site you must follow rules of acceptable use for this facility. These rules are:

  * In your postings to trefootball.com, you may not use abusive, profane, derogatory, racist, inflammatory, sexist, ageist, or other unacceptable language. The language must be of a ‘G’ rating.
  * Your postings to trefootball.com are subject to approval for publication – they are not shown on the site until approved. We reserve the right to adjust text or delete the posting.

If you breach any terms of use we reserve the right to block your ISP from visiting trefootball.com

By visiting or posting to trefootball.com, you are agreeing to these rules. 

### Must Read

#### Abuse allegations against...

Ohio State’s Running back, Bri’onte Dunn was dismissed from the team “for a violation of team rules”, said team coach...

#### NCAA Lacrosse - Four Final...

The National Collegiate Athletic Association is a membership organization whose primary goal is to protect and advocate...

#### Top two stars of the Utah...

Utah Utes: SIAOSI AIONO was born in May, 1993 in Salt Lake City, Utah, U.S.A. He plays in the position of Offensive...

#### North Dakota State wins a...

North Dakota is an amazing football team, and they have proved this over the past few years. The new additions to the...

### Recently Published

### Post of the week

  * 

## ViewMore

In this day and age when everybody seems to rely...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

When many think of swimming, they aren’t...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

Rhythmic breathing is essential when performing...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

Yoga itself is an art and it is entirely...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

There are exercises which are focused to...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

There are a number of exercises, combined with...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

Everyone tends to gain fat on the upper arms, but...

View more

  * 

## ViewMore

Exercise can seem like a very hectic task for...

View more
